{
    "J":[
        {
            "topic": "Variables",

            "question": "Which of these is a valid variable name in Java?", 
            "answers":["_int", "int", "1stNumber"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Encapsulation",
    
            "question": "Which of these is not a access modifier in Java?", 
            "answers":["global", "public", "private", "protected", "default"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Objects",
    
            "question": "Which of these is the correct keyword for instantiating a Java class?", 
            "answers":["new", "create", "There is no keyword", "instance"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "How many primitive classes are there in Java?", 
            "answers":["6", "4", "5", "8"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "How many bits is a long in Java?", 
            "answers":["64", "48", "32", "128"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "What is the default value of a long in Java?", 
            "answers":["0", "1", "-1", "null"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "How many bits is an int in Java?", 
            "answers":["32", "48", "64", "128"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "What is the default value of an int in Java?", 
            "answers":["0", "1", "-1", "null"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "How many bits is a short in Java?", 
            "answers":["16", "64", "32", "128"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Variables",
    
            "question": "What is the default value of a short in Java?", 
            "answers":["0", "1", "-1", "null"]
        },

        {
            "topic": "Objects",
    
            "question": "Java is a statically-typed language. True or False?", 
            "answers":["True", "False"]
        }

        

    ],
 
    "P":[
        {
            "topic": "Variables",

            "question": "Which of these is a not a primitive data type in Python?", 
            "answers":["double", "float", "string", "int", "bool"]
        }
    ],

    "shared":[

        {
            "topic": "Variables",

            "question": "Which of these variable names is in 'camel case'?",
            "answers":["myInt", "Myint", "myint", "MyInt"]
        }
    ]

}